It 's hormonal .
I mean , I don 't usually fall back on , you know ,
Women 's issues , but ...
But child-proofed how ? Gates and stuff ?
Dude , she did the drawers .
We don 't even know if this whole fertility thing is going to work .
She screwed in these little jobbies where you can 't even open the drawers .
- At all ? - No . They open , you know , like an inch .
Then you gotta dig your finger in . I mean , it 's a nightmare .
I guess sooner or later ...
Yeah , well , a lot later . She did the upper cabinets .
The kid 'll be 30 before he can reach ' em ,
Assuming , you know , we have a kid .
Attention ...
It is natural for her to feel protective .
Don 't even ... You have women 's issues .
Please . You of all people .
Oh , come on , it 's a jinx .
It ... It guarantees that we won 't get pregnant .
And it takes me about 20 minutes to get a fuckin ' beer .
Guys , guys , Stockholm went south .
Seriously ? I thought they were looking good .
What cracked ?
I haven 't seen the footage . Word is just going around .
Well , it 's never been a stable scenario .
Everyone knows you can 't trust Swedes .
That means there 's just japan ... Japan and us .
It 's not the first time it 's come down to that .
- Japan has a perfect record . - We 're # 2 . We try harder .
- Guys , if we fail ... - Please , we haven 't had a glitch since ' 98 .
We know what we 're doing , lin .
Or we have it written down ... somewhere .
You guys better not be messing around in there .
Ooh , does this mean you 're not in the betting pool this year ?
Big money .
I am just saying it 's a key scenario .
No , I hear what you 're saying .
In ' 98 , it was the Chem Department 's fault , right ?
Where do you work again ? Wait , it 's coming back to me now .
It 's gonna be a long weekend
if everyone 's that puckered up .
So you wanna come over Monday night ?
I 'm gonna pick up some power drills , liberate my cabinets .
Are you even listening to me ?
# You never get that taste out of your mouth #
# You never get the paw print out of the hen house now #
# And you can 't go back the same way you came #
# Round all the pieces up #
# But they just don 't fit the same #
# Right now ' cause maybe it 's not so bad #
# So let your hair down now ... #
Ugh ! Professor Fuckwad .
Why haven 't you stuck that asshole 's picture on the dartboard yet ?
It 's not that simple . Oh , my god .
- Your hair ... It 's blond . - Very fabulous , no ?
- I can 't believe you did it . - But very fabulous , right ?
Hurry up with the " very fabulous " .
I 'm getting insecure about it now .
Oh , god . No , no . It looks awesome .
- Curt 's gonna lose it . - Oh , Curt 's gonna thank me .
And so will you while we are burning this picture .
Oh , not ready .
Seriously , this isn 't his fault .
What 's not his fault ?
Fucking his student or breaking up with her by email ?
- I knew what I was getting into . - Oh , please .
You know what you 're getting into this weekend ?
This .
And if Holden 's as cute as Curt says he is ,
Possibly getting out of it .
That is the last thing that I want .
If you guys treat this like a set-Up , I 'm gonna have no fun at all .
I 'm not pushing . But we 're packing this .
Which means we definitely won 't have room for ...
What if I get bored ?
These 'll help ?
" Soviet economic structures " ?
" Aftermath of the ca ... " No .
We have a lake and a cake . No more learning !
Think fast . Ooh , faster than that .
Sorry , sorry . Move along .
- Nice ! - Is that Holden ?
we 'll be right down !
He just transferred from state .
Best hands on the team . He 's a sweet guy .
- And he 's good with his hands . - Hey !
I 'm kind of seeing this girl ,
But you 're way blonder than she is .
But I was thinking , you know , maybe ...
What is this ?
What are these ? What are you doing with these ?
Okay , I get it . I 'll leave the books .
No , no . Who gave you these ? Who taught you about these ?
I learned it from you , okay ? I learned it from watching you !
Okay , seriously , professor Bennett ...
He covers this whole book in his lectures .
You should read this .
Gurovsky . Now , this is way more interesting .
Also , Bennett doesn 't know it by heart ,
So he 'll think you 're insightful .
And you have no pants .
Oh , shit !
- That pretty much it ? - Fuckin ' better be .
You know , Jules , it 's a weekend , not an evacuation .
Trust me when I say there is nothing in those cases
you won 't be glad I brought .
I 'm shutting right up .
Oh , my god .
# In the backseat screaming out loud #
# In the backseat screaming out ... #
Marty .
What the fuck is wrong with you , bro ?
People in this town drive in a very counterintuitive manner .
That 's what I have to say .
Do you want to spend the weekend in jail ?
' Cause we 'd all like to check out my cousin 's country home .
Marty , honey , that 's not okay .
Statistical fact :
Cops will never pull over a man with a huge bong in his car .
Why ? They fear this man .
They know he sees farther than they ,
And he will bind them with ancient logics .
Have you gone gray ?
You 're not bringing that thing in the rambler .
What ? A giant bong in your father 's van ?
What are you , stoned ?
Hey , man .
Dana , you fetching minx !
Do you have any food ?
Everybody ready ?
- Whoo ! - Yeah !
- Yeah ? - Okay , I 'm ready .
Let 's get this show on the road .
Fuck , yeah !
# The static comes in slow #
# You can feel it grow #
# Our stream of conscience flows ... #
The nest is empty . We 're right on time .
I hope this is the right road .
It doesn 't even show up on the G.P.S.
It is unworthy of global positioning .
That 's the whole point ...
Get off the grid , right ?
No cell phone reception ,
No traffic cameras .
Go someplace for one goddamn weekend
where they can 't globally position my ass , man .
You can ... This is the whole issue .
Is society crumbling , Marty ?
No , society is binding .
Right ? It 's filling in the cracks with concrete .
Everything 's filed or recorded or blogged , right ?
Chips in our kids ' heads so they won 't get lost ?
Society needs to crumble .
We 're all just too chicken shit to let it .
I 've missed your rants .
You will come to see things my way .
- Identification , please . - Security team 6 ...
Mr. Sitterson .
Mr. Hadley . Thank you .
- What 's your name ? - Daniel Truman , sir .
This isn 't the military , Truman . You can drop the " sir " .
But Sitterson does like to be called ma 'am .
- Or honey toes . - He will also answer to honey toes .
You clear on what 's going to be happening here ?
I 've been prepped extensively .
And did they tell you that being prepped
- is not the same thing as being prepared ? - They told me .
- I 'll hold my post , Mr. Hadley . - Good man .
Okay , system 's online .
Acquiring target . Let 's see what we got .
All right .
I 'm thinking this thing doesn 't take credit cards .
I don 't think it knows about money .
I think it 's barter gas .
Hello ?
say , Holden .
Holden !
I don 't think there 's gonna be any ...
You come here uninvited ?
Fuck !
Dude .
Sign says " closed " .
We were looking to buy some gas .
Does this pump work ?
If you know how to work it .
We also wanted to get directions .
- Yeah , we 're looking for ... What 's it called ? - Tillerman road .
Do you know if it 's this way ?
Tillerman road takes you up the hill there ,
Dead ends at the old Buckner place .
My cousin bought a house up there .
You go through , like , a mountain tunnel ; there 's a lake .
- Would that be the ... - Buckner place .
Always someone looking to sell that plot .
You knew the original owners ?
Yeah , not the first .
I seen plenty come and go .
- Hell , I been here since the war . - Which war ?
You know damn well which war .
Would that have been with the blue
and some in gray ,
Brother perhaps fighting against brother in that war ?
You sassin ' me , boy ?
You were rude to my friend .
That whore ?
What 'd you say ?
I think we got enough gas .
You got enough to get you there .
Getting back ... That 's your concern .
Well , good luck with your business , sir .
I know the railroad 's coming through here any day now .
That 's gonna be big .
Streets paved with actual street .
Fucker .
Guys , take a look .
This must be it .
Oh , my god , it 's , uh , beautiful .
One spider and I 'm sleeping in the rambler .
I mean it .
Come on , give me a hand .
Ho ho ! This is awesome .
It is kinda cool .
Hey , you gonna kill us a raccoon to eat ?
I 'll use its skin to make a cap .
Everybody get your suits on .
- In 10 minutes , we 're hitting the lake . - Yeah .
I was not informed there would be calisthenics .
Yeah , I don 't think so .
Whoa .
No way .
Nah ... Ah , shit .
Um , this is happening .
Uh ...
Hold up !
You 've got to be fucking kidding me .
That 's just creepy .
It was pioneer days .
People had to make their own interrogation rooms .
Who did your cousin buy this place from ?
We should check the rest of the rooms and make sure this is the only one .
' Cause you know Marty wants to watch us pounding away .
I didn 't even like hearing that .
Don 't be an ape , Curt .
How about we switch ?
Not that I 'd ... I mean , I 'd put the picture back ,
But you might feel better if we switched rooms .
I really would .
Thanks for , uh , being decent .
It 's the least I could do
since Curt and Jules sold you to me for marriage .
Um , they 're not subtle .
Well , I 'll just be flattered and keep it to myself .
Yeah , I 'm not looking for ... But I 'm still grateful
that you 're not a creep .
Let 's not jump to any conclusions there .
I had kind of an internal debate about showing you the mirror ...
Shouting on both sides , blood was spilled .
So you 're bleeding internally .
Pretty bad .
Well , Jules is pre-Med . You should probably talk to her .
Uh , o-Okay .
Whoa .
Oh . Ooh , ooh , ooh .
Yeah , I don 't think so .
Yeah ...
Very clean , Curt ...
You gonna get the rest ?
Are you gonna help ?
I gotta say , I like my room .
Places , everyone .
We are live .
Engineering , we 've got a room change ...
Polk is now in 2 , McCrea is in 4 .
Operations , do you copy ? We need a scenario adjustment .
- I 'll have it back to you in 15 . - Miss lin .
We 've got the blood work back on louden .
Her levels are good , but we 're recommending
a 50mg bump of Rhohyptase to increase libido .
- Sold . - Do we pipe it in or do you want to do it orally ?
Oh , ask me that again , only slower .
You 're a pig . Guess how we 're slowing down cognition .
I don 't know .
- The hair dye . - Dumb blonde .
- Very artistic . - Works its way into the blood
through the scalp ... Very gradual .
The Chem Department keeps their end up .
I 'll see it when I believe it .
- Control ? - Yeah , go ahead .
Uh , I have the harbinger on line 2 .
Oh , Christ . Can you take a message ?
Uh , I don 't think so .
He 's really pushy .
Um , to be honest , he 's kind of freaking me out .
Okay , put him on .
Mordecai , baby , what 's happening ?
How 's the weather up top ?
The lambs have passed through the gate .
They are come to the killing floor .
Well , you 're doing a great job out there .
By the numbers , man . You got us started off just right .
So we 'll talk to you later , okay ?
Their blind eyes see nothing of the horrors to come .
Their ears are stopped .
They are the gods ' fools .
Well , that 's how it works .
Cleanse them . Cleanse the world
of their ignorance and sin .
Bathe them in the crimson of ...
Am I on speakerphone ?
No , absolutely not .
Speakerphone ? No . No , I wouldn 't do that .
Yes , I am . I can hear the echo .
Oh , my god . You 're right .
Hang on one second . I 'll take you off .
That 's rude . I don 't know who 's in the room .
Fine , there ... You 're off .
Thank you .
Don 't take this lightly , boy .
It wasn 't all by your numbers .
The fool nearly derailed the invocation with his insolence .
The ancient ones see everything .
And they will not be ...
I 'm still on speakerphone , aren 't i ?
Oh , my god , Mordecai !
I can 't believe it . It did it again .
Mordy ?
What happens next ?
Whoo !
Ah !
Oh , that 's cold !
Whoo , that 's what cold feels like !
Yeah , how cold ? Is it worth it ?
Come on , Jules . Life is risk .
Yeah , I might just risk laying out in the sun for a while .
Boo .
- Hey , what is that ? - What ?
- In the lake right there . - Oh , come on .
Guys , I 'm serious , right there . There , there !
God , it looks just like my girlfriend .
Oh , my god !
There 's something else in the lake .
- It 's a gorgeous man ! - I 'm gonna kill you !
Don 't kill the gorgeous man . We 're endangered .
All right , last chance . It 's post time .
Dig deep , people . Betting windows are closing .
Okay , who 's still out ?
Uh , let 's see ... We 've got Engineering , we 've got RD ,
- And we 've got Electrical . - Did you see who they picked ?
They 're practically giving their money away .
You should talk , Aquaman .
- What do you mean ? - Aw , nothing .
Okay , all right .
I 'm not even sure we have one of these .
Zoology swears we do .
Well , they 'd know . Okay , all right , people .
Hey , what do you got ?
No , they 've already been picked .
What ? No . Who took them ?
- Maintenance . - Maintenance ?
- They pick the same thing every year . - What do you want from me ?
If they were creative , they wouldn 't be in maintenance .
Now , you 're gonna have to split this if you win . You wanna switch ?
Um , I don 't know . I don 't know .
What do you think ?
More than anything I just want this moment to end .
Not betting ?
Not for me . Thanks .
Seems a little harsh , doesn 't it ?
It 's just people letting off steam .
This job isn 't easy , however those clowns may behave .
Does the director ... Do they know about this downstairs ?
The director doesn 't care about this stuff ,
As long as everything goes smoothly upstairs ,
As long as the kids do as they are told ...
But then it 's fixed .
No , no , no .
How can you wager on this when you control the outcome ?
No , we just get them in the cellar . They take it from there .
No , they have to make the choice of their own free will .
Otherwise the system doesn 't work .
Just like the harbinger .
He 's this creepy old fuck ,
Practically wears a sign : " You will die " .
Why do we put him there ? The system .
They have to choose to ignore him ,
And they have to choose what happens in the cellar .
Yeah , we rig the game as much as we need to ,
But in the end , they don 't transgress ...
They can 't be punished .
So what 's it going to be , Truman ? You in ?
Window 's closing .
I 'm fine .
Okay , that 's it , gang .
The board is locked !
Oh , let 's get this party started .
Let 's get this party started !
Okay , who wants some beer ? Here you go .
Okay , my turn . Jules ?
Mmm ?
Truth or dare ?
- Let 's go dare . - All right .
I dare you to make out with ...
Please say Dana . Please say Dana . Please say Dana .
... that moose over there .
Marty , have you ever seen a moose before ?
Whatever that mysterious beast is .
- That 's a wolf . - That 's clearly a wolf .
I 'm living in a womb of reefer . Leave me alone .
Jules , I dare you to make out with that wolf .
No problem .
Who ? Me ?
Why , yes , I am new in town .
How did you know ?
Oh , my god , that is so sweet of you to say .
I just colored it , in fact .
No , no , no , there 's no need to huff and puff .
I 'll let you come in .
Oh .
Thank you .
Yeah , baby !
- Now then , Dana ? - Truth .
What 's that supposed to mean ?
I 'm just skipping ahead .
You 're gonna say " dare " .
She 's gonna dare you to do something you don 't like .
And then you 'll puss out and say that you wanted truth all along .
Really ?
Okay , Jules , dare .
What the hell was that ?
It 's the cellar door .
The wind must have blown it open .
Uh , that makes what kind of sense ?
What do you think is down there ?
Why don 't we find out ?
Dana ...
I dare you .
How long do I have to stay down here ?
Oh , you know , just till morning .
- Ah ! - Dana ?
You okay ?
Yeah .
Sorry , I just scared myself .
Well , you called for help . That voids the dare .
Take your top off .
What ? I didn 't make up the rules .
Oh , my god .
Look at all this .
Uh , guys ...
I 'm not sure it 's awesome to be down here .
- Guys ? - Dude , seriously ,
Your cousin is into some weird shit .
Yeah , well , I 'm pretty sure this ain 't his .
Maybe it was the people who put in that mirror thing .
Some of this stuff looks really old .
It 's beautiful .
Maybe we should go back upstairs .
I dare you all to go upstairs .
Guys ?
Guys , listen to this .
" April 4th .
Father was cross with me and said I lacked the true faith .
I wish I could prove my devotion
as Judah and Matthew proved on those travelers . "
What is that ?
Diary of Anna Patience Buckner ,
1903 .
" Mama screamed most of the night .
I prayed that she might find faith ,
But she only stopped when papa cut her belly
and stuffed the coals in .
Judah told me in my dream that Matthew took him
to the black room , so I know he is killed .
I want to understand the glory of the pain
like Matthew ,
But cutting the flesh
makes him have a husband 's bulge
and I do not get like that . "
- Jesus , can we not ... - No , go on .
- Why ? - I want to know .
" I have found it ...
In the oldest books , the way of saving our family .
My good arm is hacked up and ' et '
so I hope this will be readable .
But a believer will come
and speak this to our spirits .
Then we will be restored and the great pain will return . "
And then ... Then there 's something in Latin .
Okay , I 'm drawing a line in the fucking sand here .
Do not read the Latin .
Read it .
- What the fuck ? - Read it out loud .
No , no , no .
Stop being a fucking baby .
- Curt . - It 's a diary .
It doesn 't even mean anything .
Dana .
We have a winner !
It 's the buckers , ladies and gentlemen .
The buckers pull a " W " .
All right , that means that congratulations
go to Maintenance
who share the pot with Ronald the intern .
- Yeah ! Whoo ! - Wait , that 's not fair . I had zombies , too .
Yes , you did . Yes , you had zombies .
But this is " zombie redneck torture family " . See ?
They 're entirely separate species .
It 's like the difference between an elephant and an elephant seal .
There 's always next year .
They 're like something from a nightmare .
No , they 're something nightmares are from .
Everything in our stable is remnant of the old world ,
Courtesy of you know who .
Monsters ? Magic ? Gods ?
You get used to it .
Should you ?
Oh , man , I 'm sorry .
- He had the conch in his hands . - I know .
You know , a couple more minutes ,
Who knows what might have happened ?
I am never gonna see a merman , ever .
Dude , be thankful . Those things are terrifying .
And the clean-Up on ' em is a nightmare .
So the Buckners again .
Well , they may be zombified ,
Pain-Worshipping backwoods idiots .
But they 're our zombified , pain-Worshipping backwoods idiots .
- With 100 % clearance rate . - True .
So should we call japan ?
Tell them to take the rest of the weekend off ?
Yeah , right . They 're Japanese .
What are they gonna do , relax ?
I 'd just like to see them fall on their asses for once .
God , don 't even joke .
Every other branch has air-Balled .
We need the Japanese crew to get it done .
There 's too much riding on this .
# Can 't get you out of my head #
# Thinking about you while I 'm lying in bed #
# Your fingertips are craving , got me misbehaving #
# And all I want to do is scream your name out #
# I want your desire ... #
Fuck , yeah , baby .
This is so classy .
Come on , like you wouldn 't want a piece of that .
Can we not talk about people and pieces anymore tonight ?
Oh , are you feeling lonely , Marty ?
Marty and I were sweeties in our freshman hall .
We made out once .
I never did buy that ring .
But we 're still ...
Close .
I have a theory about all this .
That 's our cue to bail .
Tommy Chong here has a theory .
Come on , baby .
Don 't worry , you can tell it to egghead here
if he 's not too busy devirginizing Dana .
Jules , do you want to go lie down ?
That 's exactly the point . Come on .
- Mush , mush ! - Don 't push me around .
Not around , baby . It 's a straight line .
You seriously believe nothing weird is going on ?
Conspiracy ?
The way everybody is acting .
Why is Jules suddenly a celebutard ?
And since when does Curt pull this alpha-Male bullshit ?
I mean , he 's a sociology major .
He 's on full academic scholarship
and now he 's calling his friend an egghead ?
Curt 's just drunk .
I 've seen Curt drunk .
Jules , too .
Well , then , maybe it 's something else .
What ?
You 're not seeing what you don 't want to see .
Puppeteers .
Puppeteers ?
Pop-Tarts ?
Did you say you have pop-Tarts ?
Marty , I love you , but you 're really high .
We are not who we are .
I 'm gonna go read a book with pictures .
Thank you . " The pain outlives the flesh .
The flesh returns or re ... Has a meeting place . "
What is that ?
The Latin that you read ...
You speak Latin ?
Not well . Not since 10th grade .
Weird how it all comes back .
Well , it 's a weird kind of night .
I 'm sorry about tonight . Everybody ...
Do I lose points if I tell you I 'm having a pretty nice time ?
No .
You can tell me that .
What are you running away for ?
Ah !
Don 't spill on me .
Oh , did I get a little beer on your shirt ?
I guess it 'll have to come off , huh ?
- Not here . - Oh , baby , come on .
We 're all alone .
I 'm chilly .
Okay , guys , that 's it .
Let 's go . We 've got a job to do .
Your basic human needs disgust me . Get out of here .
Do we have temperature control in this sector ?
On it .
Engaging pheromone mists .
It 's so dark . Take me inside .
Baby , come on , this is why we came here .
It 's romantic .
Okay , baby , let 's see some boobies .
Show us the goods .
Does it really matter if we see ...
We 're not the only ones watching , kid .
Gotta keep the customer satisfied .
You understand what 's at stake here ?
Oh .
Score .
Jules !
Fuck .
- Curt ! - Ah !
Oh , fuck .
Curt !
No . No .
What are you ... What are you gonna do to me ?
- No ! - Curt !
This we offer in humility and fear
for the blessed peace of your eternal slumber .
- As it ever was . - As it ever was .
Nemo , man , you gotta wake up .
Your shit is topsy-Turvy .
I 'm gonna go for a walk .
Okay , I swear to fucking god somebody is talking .
Or I 'm pretty sure someone is . Oh .
I 'm gonna go for a walk .
Enough !
What are you saying , huh ?
What do you want ?
You think I 'm a puppet , huh ?
You think I 'm a puppet ,
Gonna do a little fuckin ' puppet dance ?
I 'm the boss of my own brain , so give it up .
I 'm gonna go for a walk .
I don 't want to ... I mean , I 've never ...
I don 't mean " never " .
Hey , nothing you don 't want .
He 's got a husband bulge .
I thought there 'd be stars .
We are abandoned .
- Ah ! - Fuckin ' run !
- Whoa ! - Curt !
Dead bitch .
Jesus ! What the fuck ?
Curt , what the fuck ?
- Where are you hurt ? Is all of this from you ? - Hold on , hold on !
- Where 's ... - Curt , you 're okay .
Where 's Jules ?
She 's gone .
We gotta get out of here .
No ! No , wait .
- Dana , don 't open that . - I 'm not leaving here without Jules .
That dead girl 's out there !
Dana , come on !
- What is that thing ? - Fuck .
- I don 't know , but there 's more of them . - More of them ?
I saw a young girl ,
All zombied like him .
But she was missing an arm .
Oh , my god .
Patience .
The diary .
- Look , we gotta lock this place down . - He 's right .
We 'll go room by room , barricade every window and door .
We gotta play it safe .
No matter what happens , we have to stay together .
- Fuck ! - Calm down .
Watch the master work .
- This isn 't right . - What ? What 's the matter ?
Th ... This isn 't right . We should split up .
We can cover more ground that way .
Yeah .
Yeah , good idea .
Really ?
Guys ... You guys , get in your rooms .
Lock ' em in .
Huh ? What ... What the fuck ?
Ah !
Shit . Oh .
What the ...
What the fuck ?
Uh-Oh , that 's not good .
Out of the way . Out of the way . Out of the way .
Chem Department , I need 500 ccs of Thorazine pumped into room 3 .
- No , no , no , no , no , no . - Stand by , chem .
Judah Buckner to the rescue .
What the fuck ?
What the fuck ? What the fuck ? !
Oh , my god .
I 'm on a reality TV show .
My parents are gonna think I 'm such a burnout .
Ah ! Fuck !
Ah ! Help !
Ah !
No , no !
Help me ! Help me !
Must be getting excited downstairs .
Greatest show on earth .
Somebody help me !
Come on !
- Ah ! Move the bed . - Come on , come on .
Holden .
- It 's empty . - Go .
- Curt ? - Unlock the door .
I can 't . Get down to the basement .
This is the black room .
Nice .
From the diary .
This is where he killed them .
This is where he kills us .
Oh , hey , no . He 's not gonna kill us .
We just gotta find a door .
Okay ?
Let 's just check the walls , okay ?
Curt ?
I mean , there 's got to be some ...
Ah ! No !
You like pain ?
How 's that work for you ?
Oh , these fucking zombies .
Remember when you could just throw a girl in a volcano ?
How old do you think I am ?
Let 's move ! Come on ! Come on , let 's go !
What about Marty ?
They got him .
Fuck you !
Fuck you , fuck you , fuck you ,
Fuck you , fuck you .
- You seeing this ? - Perfect record , huh ?
The japan crew should have had this in the bag .
They fucked us . How hard is it to kill nine-Year-Olds ?
Zero fatality , total wash .
I 'm telling you , you want good product ,
You gotta buy American .
Any word from downstairs ?
Downstairs doesn 't care about japan .
- The director trusts us . - Hey , you just sweat the Chem , lin .
While these morons are singing " what a friend we have in Shinto , "
we are bringing the pain .
Yeah , and what the fuck 's up with this guy 's pot anyway ?
Now he 's supposed to be drooling ,
And instead he almost makes us ?
We treated the shit out of it .
Okay , we got the rambler heading toward the tunnel .
The fool 's toast anyway .
And so are we if you don 't get this under control .
- Shit . - What ? " Shit " why ?
- Gotta go . Work to do . - You guys are humanity 's last hope .
If the ancients rise , we ...
- There 's no cave-In . - What ?
The fucking tunnel 's open !
- Control to demolition . - We 're dark in the whole sector .
- Try to bypass it . - What the fuck do you think I 'm doing ?
Okay , open the door .
Look out . Get out of the ...
Make a hole .
- What the fuck 's going on ? - We don 't know .
Electrical said there was a glitch ...
That tunnel should have blown hours ago .
- Well , we didn 't get the order . - Come on , come on .
Right there .
Hadley , what is going on ?
Hadley !
Why hasn 't the tunnel blown ?
No . No , no , no . No fucking way !
I can 't believe this , man . This ain 't happening .
It 's right there .
All right , we got any climbing gear , ropes ?
Yeah , in my fucking dorm room .
We can 't go back . There 's no way across ?
What are we gonna do , jump ?
Dude .
What ?
Curt , are you sure about this ?
I 've done bigger jumps than this .
You 've got a smooth run
and maybe a five-Foot differential on the other side .
But you 've got to give it everything .
Curt ...
Look , you guys , you stay in the rambler .
I 'll get help .
If I wipe out , I 'll fucking limp for help .
But I 'm coming back here .
I 'm coming back with cops and choppers
and large fuckin ' guns .
And those things are gonna pay ...
For Jules .
Don 't hold back .
I never do .
No !
Curt !
No ! Oh , god !
Oh , my god .
He hit something . There 's nothing .
What did he hit ?
Puppeteers .
Marty was right .
Get in the van .
Dana .
Marty was right .
You 're going back .
I 'm going through .
We 'll just drive .
There 's got to be another road , another way out of here .
That won 't work .
Something 'll happen . It 'll collapse , wash away .
Then we just leave the roads altogether ,
Drive as far as we can into the forest
and we go on foot from there .
You 're missing the point .
Please do not go nuts on me , okay , Dana ?
You 're all I 've got now .
I 'm okay .
Good , okay , ' cause I need you calm .
Okay , no matter what happens , we 've got to stick ...
God damn , that was close !
Yeah , photo fuckin ' finish .
I don 't understand . You 're celebrating ?
They 're celebrating . I 'm drinking .
But she 's still alive . How can the ritual be complete ?
The virgin 's death is optional as long as it 's last .
The main thing is that she , you know , suffers .
That she did .
It 's so strange .
I 'm actually rooting for this girl .
She 's got so much heart .
You think of all the pain and the ...
# Tequila is my lady ! My lady ! #
Come on in , guys . Come on in , come on in .
You 're welcome . Tequila !
From darkness there is light .
Ah !
# As soon as you are able #
# Woman , I am willin ' #
# To make the break that we are on the brink of #
# My cup is on the table #
# My love is spillin ' #
# Waiting here for you to take and drink of ... #
I wish that I could do what you do .
- Oh , my god . - Yeah , it 's masterful .
Oh , I don 't know . You know , tonight was solid . I don 't know .
Are you kidding ? Classic denouement .
- When the van hits the lake ... - I screamed .
- Right ? - And the water rushing in and the zombie ...
Primal terror .
I just think it would 've been cooler with a merman .
Do you know if we get the overtime bonus on this one ?
Accounting 's over there . Ask them .
I don 't need to . I already know the answer .
I 'm an intern .
So I don 't qualify for O.T.
It 's funny that you like the ballet ,
Because I happen to have two tickets
to your favorite ...
You knuckleheads .
You almost gave me a heart attack with that tunnel .
Like I said , it wasn 't our fault . We didn 't get the order .
I 'm just giving you a hard time .
come on . Give us a hug .
- Hey . - No , seriously , that wasn 't our fault .
There was a glitch ... A power reroute from upstairs .
What do you mean , upstairs ?
Turn the fucking music off .
Hello ?
That 's impossible . Everything was done within the guidelines .
The virgin 's the only one .
No , I am not doubting you .
Which one ?
- Marty ? - Hi .
Dana !
Dana , come on .
Oh !
Marty , wait , we 're going in the grave ?
Dana , come on !
What is this place ?
Whoa , whoa . Whoa , whoa , okay .
Yeah , I had to dismember that guy with a trowel .
What have you been up to ?
Nobody else , huh ?
Yeah .
Yeah , I figured .
You figured everything .
No , not at all .
But I do know some stuff .
As in ...
It 's an elevator .
Somebody sent those dead fucks up here to get us .
Now , there 's no controls inside ,
But there 's maintenance overrides in there .
And I think I can get it to go down .
Do we want to go down ?
Where else are we gonna go ?
Here .
Okay , okay , okay .
Yeah .
Ah ! Come on !
Fucking zombie arm !
Oh , shit .
Shit .
Oh , my god .
What the ...
We chose .
What ? What ?
What ? Oh .
Fuck .
In the cellar .
All that shit we were playing with .
They made us choose .
They made us choose how we die .
We saw them go down the access drop .
They have to be in one of these .
Internal security could ...
I don 't care if it 's not protocol . Are you fucking high ?
It 's the fool . Do not touch the girl .
If he outlives her , this whole thing goes to hell .
Take him out first .
Clean-Up says the prep team missed one of the kid 's stashes .
Whatever he 's been smoking has been immunizing him to all our shit .
How does that help us right now ? What ?
No , if you have a confirmed kill , take her out , too .
- There ! - 3606 .
- Gotcha . - Bring ' em down .
Out of the elevator ! Step out of the elevator !
- Why are you trying to kill us ? - Step out .
- Just the girl . - Just me ?
Do it !
No !
Ah !
Good work , zombie arm .
You shouldn 't be here .
This should have gone differently ,
Ended more quickly .
I can only imagine your pain and confusion .
But know this :
What 's happening to you is part of something bigger ,
Something older than anything known .
You 've seen horrible things ,
An army of nightmare creatures .
But they are nothing compared to what came before ,
What lies below .
It 's our task to placate the ancient ones ,
As it 's yours to be offered up to them .
Forgive us and let us get it over with .
Go on . Go , go , go , go .
Army of nightmares , huh ?
Let 's get this party started .
Hold your fire !
Oh , shit .
Go , go , go !
Out there ! Spread out !
We need men now !
Ah !
Please don 't cut ...
Get the fucker off me !
Lead officer Truman to security command ,
Requesting immediate reinforcements . Code black .
I repeat : Code black .
Where the fuck are you guys ?
Sector 12 down . Sector 8 down .
- Sector 3 down . - Jesus Christ !
Why aren 't the defenses working ? Where 's the fucking gas ?
Something chewed through the connections in the utility shaft .
- Something which ? - Something scary !
Oh !
The north exit is blocked . You can 't go there !
Where are you going ?
# Hush , little baby , don 't say a word ... #
Go , go , go . Go .
Ooh .
Fuck , we 're running out of time !
It 's on lockdown . I 'm trying to bypass .
Oh !
Hadley !
Aw , come on !
- Oh , my god . - God .
No , no !
Gah ! Oh .
It 's you .
No , no , please , please , please , please .
Kill him .
Okay , Dana , come on .
Dana .
Here , it 's easier with this .
Look at these .
Five of them .
What are they ?
Us .
I should have seen it like you did .
This is part of a ritual .
A ritual sacrifice ?
Great . You tie someone to a stone ,
Get a fancy dagger and a bunch of robes .
- It 's not that complicated . - No .
It 's simple .
They don 't just want to see us killed .
They want to see us punished .
Punished for what ?
For being young .
It 's different in every culture .
And it has changed over the years ,
But it has always required youth .
There must be at least five .
The whore ... She 's corrupted .
She dies first .
The athlete .
The scholar .
The fool .
All suffer and die at the hands of ...
Whatever horror they have raised ,
Leaving the last to live or die
as fate decides ...
The virgin .
Me ? Virgin ?
We work with what we have .
But what if you don 't pull it off ?
- They rise . - Who does ?
What 's beneath us ?
The ancient ones ... The gods that used to rule the earth .
As long as they accept our sacrifice ,
They remain below .
But the other rituals have all failed .
The sun is coming up in eight minutes .
If you live to see it , the world will end .
Maybe that 's the way it should be .
If you 've got to kill all my friends to survive ,
Maybe it 's time for a change .
We 're not talking about change .
We 're talking about the agonizing death
of every human soul on the planet ,
Including you .
You can die with them
or you can die for them .
Gosh , they 're both so enticing .
Wow .
The whole world , Marty .
Is in your hands , Dana .
There is no other way .
You have to be strong .
Yeah , Dana ,
You feeling strong ?
I 'm sorry .
So am i .
I got it !
Marty .
Ah .
Hey .
You know ...
I don 't think Curt even has a cousin .
Huh .
How are you ?
Going away .
I 'm sorry .
I 'm so sorry I almost shot you .
I probably wouldn 't have .
Hey , hey , no . Shh . No .
I totally get it .
I 'm sorry I let you get attacked by a werewolf
and then ended the world .
No .
You were right .
Humanity ...
It 's time to give someone else a chance .
Giant evil gods .
I wish I could have seen them .
I know .
That would have been a fun weekend .
# Gave up trying to figure it out #
# But my head got lost along the way #
# Worn out from giving it up #
# My soul , I pissed it all away #
# Still stings these shattered nerves #
# Pigs , we get what pigs deserve #
# I 'm going all the way down , I 'm leaving today #
# Come , come , come on , you 've gotta fill me up #
# Come , come , gotta let me inside you #
# Come , come , come on , you gotta fix me up #
# Still feel it all slipping away #
# But it doesn 't matter anymore #
# Everybody 's still slipping away #
# Look through these blackened eyes #
# You 'll see 10,000 lies #
# My lips may promise , but my heart is a whore #
# Come , come , come on , you 've gotta fix me up #
# Come , come , gotta let me inside you #
# Come , come , come on , you gotta fill me up #
# Come , come , gotta let me get through to you #
# This isn 't meant to last #
# This is for right now #
# This is for right #
# I know it 's all getting away #
# And it comes to me as no surprise #
# And I know what 's coming to me #
# Is never going to arrive #
# Fresh blood through tired skin #
# New sweat to drown me in #
# Dress up this rotten carcass #
# Just to make it look alive #
# Come , come , come on , you 've gotta fill me up #
# Come , come , gotta let me inside you #
# Come , come , come on , you gotta fix me up #
# Come , come , gotta let me get through to you #
# This isn 't meant to last #
# This is for right now #
# This is for right #
# I wish I could put the blame on you #
# I want you to take me #
# I want you to break me #
# Then I want you to throw me away #
# I wish I could put the blame on you #
# I want you to take me #
# I want you to break me #
# Then I want you to throw me away #
# I wish I could put the blame on you #
# I want you to take me #
# I want you to break me #
# Then I want you to throw me away . #